-嘿  -嘿
- Hey. - Hi.
菲比  出了什么事吗
Pheebs, what's wrong?
戴着这个超大订婚戒指
I'm just so exhausted from dragging around
快要把我累死了
this huge engagement ring.
噢  天啊
Oh, my God.
恭喜
Congratulations.
他有没有跪下来
So did he get on one knee?
他有准备求婚词吗
Did he have a speech prepared?
噢  他有哭吗
Oh, did he cry?
没错  我喜欢求婚  很奇怪吗
Yeah, big surprise, I like proposals.
实在是很温馨
Well, it was really sweet,
是我人生中最浪漫的一刻
and, like, the most romantic thing ever.
嘿  我们来敬菲比
Here's to Phoebe,
为了她找到世界上最好的男人干一杯
who's found the greatest guy in the world.
敬菲比和...
To Phoebe and--
应该是迈克吧
I want to say "Mike"?
敬菲比和迈克
To Phoebe and Mike.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
对了  我有点东西要给你
Oh, and I have something for you.
这是我的小黑本本
It's my little black book.
里面有我约会过所有男生的电话
It's got the numbers of all the guys I've dated.
噢  菲比  很谢谢你
Oh, Phoebe, that's nice,
但我想我用不上了
but you know what? I think I'm okay.
你还是把它送给你
Why don't you just give it
其他独身的女性朋友吧
to one of your other single girlfriends.
我也想  但你是最后一个独身的了
I would, but you're the last one.
那给我吧
Give me the book!
巴布罗·迪亚斯
"Pablo Diaz.
布里迪·史密斯
Brady Smith.
"开货车的男生"
Guy in Van"?
那是我的初恋
Oh, my first love.
巴伯·格里莫的名字旁边
What is the red X next to
标着个红叉是什么意思
Bob Gremore's name mean?
挂了
Dead.
没关系  他已经很老了
Oh, it's okay. No, he was old. Yeah.
他经历相当丰富
And he lived a full life.
奥马哈登陆  他第一波上去的
He was in the first wave at Omaha Beach.
嘿  对不起  我结婚时也应该
oh, I'm sorry. I should've given you guys my black book
把我的电话本给你们男生的
when I got married.
尽管那不算是电话本
Although, it wasn't so much a book
只是一张皱皱的纸...
as a napkin.
...上面写着珍妮斯的电话
With Janice's phone number on it.
菲比  杰思罗·塔尔不是一个乐队吗
Phoebe, isn't Jethro Tull a band?
没错
Oh, yes, they are.
嘿  老婆
Hey, honey.
嘿  老公
Hey, sweetie.
-莫尼卡不在吗  -不在
- Is Monica not here? - No.
那我先告诉你吧
Then I'll tell you.
我们公司中标了一个大广告订单
My agency was bidding for a big account, and they got it.
这是我第一个跨国广告
It's my first national commercial.
酷
Cool.
不是我吹牛
And I don't want to brag,
但很多内容都是我构思出来的
but a lot of the ideas were mine.
去他的  你又没在那
Hell, you weren't there.
全部构思都是我的
All the ideas were mine.
太好了
That's great.
嘿  可以介绍我去拍广告吗
Hey, can you cast me in it?
...不知道啊  我想你不适合里面的角色
I really don't think you're right for the part.
怎么会  我可以演任何角色
What do you mean? I can do anything.
我是一条变色龙呢
I'm a chameleon.
我很老
I'm old.
我很累
I'm tired.
嘿  我很热  我很冷
Oh, I am hot. I'm cold.
拜托  有什么我不能演
Come on, what can't I do?
我得说  精彩...
First of all, bravo.
但我觉得你真的不适合
But I don't think you're right for this.
这个角色是一个死板的大学教授
The part's a stuffy college professor.
也可以啊
I can do that.
你好  我是你们的教授
Hello, I'm your professor.
当我停下来没想重要事情的时候...
When I'm not busy thinking of important things,
或者没在教授的时候...
or professing...
我会用...  噢  是什么产品
...l like to use-- What's the product?
电子商务网络解决方案
Software that facilitates inter-business networking e-solutions.
我很冷
I'm cold.
-嘿  -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
猜猜谁有可能得到
Guess who's a finalist
一笔庞大的科研补助金
for a huge research grant?
给你个提示
I'll give you a hint.
他正在看着你
He's looking right at you.
除非你说的是
Well, unless it's the creepy guy
那个把手伸入他裙子的怪人
with his hand up his kilt...
我要说  恭喜你
...I'm gonna say, "Congratulations."
我实在是太兴奋了
I'm so excited.
我击败了其他的几百个竞争者
Apparently, I beat out hundreds of other applicants...
包括我上研究生时的五个同学
...including five guys I went to graduate school with.
不是我吹嘘  但...五个人
Not that I'm keeping score, or anything. Five.
-哇  太厉害了  -是啊
- Wow, that's great. - Yeah.
那个是什么补助金
So tell me about the grant.
那是两万五千元的资金
Well, okay, it's for $25,000.
如果我得到了
And if I get it,
那我就可以完成我那领域的研究了
I'll be able to complete my field research.
然后我就可以在《古生物学刊》里
And there will be an article about me
发表我的论文了
in the Paleontology Review.
那将会是我头一次在那本书上发表论文
It'll be the first time my name is in there...
而其他人就不会怀疑我的研究了
...without people raising serious questions about my work.
等等  你是说杜瓦补助金
Are you talking about the Dewer Grant?
没错  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
本杰明·哈伯特管理着那个补助金
Benjamin Hobart is administering that grant.
-你的前任男朋友  -对
- Your ex-boyfriend? - Yeah.
那么说  你的前男友决定了
So your ex-boyfriend is gonna determine
你现任男友是否能得到那笔钱
if your new boyfriend gets this grant?
你的现任男友完蛋了
Wow, your new boyfriend is screwed.
没有  我们很愉快地分手
No. No, we ended on great terms.
我意思是  如果对此事有影响的话
I mean if anything,
那也肯定是帮助你的
I think this could help you. You know what?
我们可以把他约出来吃个饭啊
Why don't we all go out to dinner,
我可以把你介绍给他
and I can introduce you.
是吗  你觉得有帮助吗
If you think it'd help.
当然啦  我给他打电话啦
Yeah, absolutely. I'll call him.
我可以做什么去...迎合他啊
Now, is there anything I could do to butter him up?
他有什么嗜好
Anything he really likes?
他确实有严重的乳胶恋物情结
He does have a pretty serious latex fetish.
还是看看晚饭会怎么样吧
We'll see how dinner goes.
-嘿  -嘿  想去看电影吗
- Hey. - Hey, you want to go see a movie?
我已经告诉过你我今天一整天要打扫
I told you I had to spend all day clearing out stuff
好让迈克搬进来住
so Mike could move in.
-噢  对哦  -没错.
- Oh, right. - Yeah.
既然我都来了
Now that I'm here,
我就帮你清洁和收拾一下吧
I might as well help with the cleaning and organizing.
刚好我还带了打标签机
I just happen to have my label maker.
要丢弃自己的物品太难了
Oh, it's so hard to get rid of stuff.
你和钱德勒要同居的时候
Did you and Chandler make compromises
有为丢弃东西妥协过吗
when you moved in together?
钱德勒有
Chandler did.
他想你丢弃什么
What does he want you to give up?
很多东西啊
A bunch of stuff.
我最舍不得的是...
And the worst one,
他要我丢掉格拉达斯
he wants me to get rid of Gladys.
谁是格拉达斯
Who's Gladys?
多么可怕的损失
What a tragic loss.
就是说  我真的不想放弃她啊
Yeah, I really hate to give her up.
噢  我想到了  你可以带她走啊
Oh, I know. Oh, you should take her.
这样...不好吧...
I don't know.
为什么  你不喜欢她吗
What, you don't like her?
我当然喜欢她啊  有什么好不喜欢的呢
Of course I do. What's not to like?
我恨不得马上就把她拿走
I'd take her in a minute.
但我觉得你现在说放弃太早了
But I think that you're giving up too easy.
我想你应该为她而斗争
Honey, I think that you need to fight for her.
-真的  你这么觉得  -当然啦
- Really, you think? - Absolutely.
你对他说
You say to him,
对不起  迈克  没有她我就活不了
"I'm sorry, Mike, I can't live without her.
她对我来说太重要了
She means too much to me."
好的  我是该为她争取一下
Okay, I'll fight for her. Okay.
等等  我忽然想到...  如果我这样做
Oh, wait. I just realized, if I do that,
你就无法得到她了
that means you don't get her.
可恶  我怎么没想到呢
Damn it, I did not think this through.
-嘿  你们  -嘿
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
你给我的推荐有回复了吗
Oh, any word on casting yet?
乔伊  我已经说过了  你不适合那个角色
I told you, you're not right for the part.
什么意思啊
What do you mean?
瑞秋  你会不会花钱
Rach, don't I seem like a professor
买像我这样的教授介绍的电子货啊
you'd buy some kind of e-crap from?
不好意思
I'm sorry,
你说的东西估计我这辈子也不会感兴趣
this sounds like something I'm never gonna be interested in.
拜托啦
Look, come on, please?
又不是要诚心为难你
It's not like I'm asking you for some crazy favor.
我就是干这行的啊
This is what I do for a living.
我是个职业的演员呢
I am a professional actor.
迟到了两小时了
Man, I'm two hours late for work.
这里有我的一盘磁带
Here's a copy of my reel.
里面有我拍过的所有广告
It's got all the commercials that I've been in.
-乔伊...  -你就看一下吧
- Joe-- - Just watch it.
如果你不喜欢
If you don't like it,
就别给你上司就是了
don't pass it on to your bosses.
-好吧  -谢谢
- Fine. - Thank you.
-工作啦  乔伊  -可恶
- Work, Joe. - Damn it.
我该怎么办啦
What am I gonna do now?
就给你上司看看咯
Just pass the tape along.
他的确不适合演这个
He's not right for the part.
如果我推荐他
If I suggest him,
我的老板会觉得我是个白痴
my bosses will think I'm an idiot.
我希望我的老板能迟些才发现这一点
And that's something they should learn on their own.
那就告诉乔伊你看过带子
Just tell Joey that you watched the tape...
你很喜欢  但你的老板们不喜欢
...and you liked it, but your bosses didn't.
那样  你就成了好人
Then that way, you're the good guy,
坏人就是你的老板啦
and they're the bad guy.
好主意  我喜欢  老板不喜欢
That's good. I liked it, they didn't.
乔伊  看在上帝份上  去工作啦
Joey, for God's sake, go to work.
真不敢相信我马上就要见到本杰明·哈伯特
I can't believe I'm about to meet Benjamin Hobart.
我一直以为
I've always thought of him as someone I'd invite...
只有在梦中才能和他共聚晚餐呢
...to my fantasy dinner party.
他会不会带上一些
Do you think there's any chance
他喜欢的小玩偶来呢
he'll bring Christie Brinkley or C-3PO?
对不起  看来他是自己来的
Sorry, it looks like it's just him.
查莉
Charlie.
天啊  你简直太美了
My God, you look absolutely stunning.
是吗  今天我特地去了理发
Well, I am having a good hair day.
-见到你真好  -我也是
- It's so good to see you. - Oh, you too.
我没事
I'm okay.
对不起...罗斯·盖勒  本杰明·哈伯特
I'm sorry. Ross Geller, Benjamin Hobart.
很荣幸见到你
It's an honor to meet you.
我仰慕你都不知道多久了
I can't tell you how long...
我是说  你得了诺贝尔奖  喔...
...I've been an admirer of your work. I mean, that Nobel Prize.
不得不对你说
I mean, I have to tell you
你是我进入这个领域原因之一
that you're one of the reasons I got into the field.
是吗  我也久仰大名
Well, likewise.
其实没有久仰
Actually not likewise.
我今早才第一次听到你的名字
I'd never heard of you until this morning.
但为人随和没什么不好
But it's nice to be nice.
-我们坐  -好的  谢谢
- Shall we? - Yeah. Thank you.
不敢相信你选了这个餐馆
I can't believe that you chose this restaurant.
你还记得那天晚上吗
Do you remember the night?
噢天啊  我完全忘记了
Oh, my God. I completely forgot.
天啊  真不敢相信他们能让我们进门
Oh, my God, I can't believe they let us back in this place.
你当时不在场
You weren't there.
是不在  但想想都好笑
No, but, you know, it's just a funny image.
想想你们两个  在这个餐馆  还...
You know, the two of you in this restaurant with the....
罗斯  我去洗手间的时候
Ross, why don't you tell Benji
你跟本杰说说你的方案吧
about your proposal while I go to the ladies' room.
来吧  告诉我吧
So tell me about it.
我们会在彩色沙漠里进行挖掘
Okay. Well, I would like to do a dig in the Painted Desert.
因为里面有些地区还没完全挖掘
There are still several areas that haven't been fully excavated.
-和查莉分手吧  -什么
- Break up with Charlie. - What?
什么
What?
你刚才说  "和查莉分手"吗
Did you just say, "Break up with Charlie"?
可以说是  也可以说不是
Well, yes and no.
是  我是这样说了  不是的话就是说我没有不说
Yes, I did say it. And no, I didn't not say it.
你不觉得这么说有点不妥吗
Kind of inappropriate, don't you think?
对不起
Listen, I'm sorry.
因为我太久没有见她了
I just haven't seen her for so long,
以前的感觉又涌上心头
all these feelings are rushing back.
让我意识到
I'm starting to realize
我有多想念她
how much I've missed her.
我需要你和她分手
And I'm gonna need you to break up with her.
你是说真的吗
Are you serious?
如果你说行  那我就是认真的
If you say, yes, then I'm serious.
如果你说不行  那我就是开玩笑
If you say, no, then I'm joking.
-不行  -我开玩笑的
- No. - Joking it is.
嗨  对不起  我迟到了
Hi, sorry I'm late.
嘿  和迈克谈得怎样
Hey, how'd it go with Mike?
他肯让你保留那幅画吗
Is he gonna let you keep the painting?
不行  他实在很讨厌它
No, he really hates it.
但他肯让我留下我那盒头发
But he's gonna let me keep my box of human hair.
所以我只能妥协了
So you gotta pick your battles.
但好消息是  格拉达斯已经属于你了
But the good news is, Gladys is yours.
那坏消息呢
Wow, what's the bad news?
谁是格拉达斯
Who's Gladys?
她是我的手工作品
Oh, she's that work of art I made.
就是女人从相框里出来的那幅
You know, with the woman coming out of the frame.
给莫尼卡了吗
And Monica gets to keep her?
放在她房间里  羡慕嫉妒恨啊
In her house? I am so jealous.
我不知道你也想要她啊
I didn't know you wanted her too.
我...当然想要啊
Well, I mean, sure, of course.
但...你已经给了莫尼卡了  所以...
But you already gave that to Monica, so....
为了你  我可以放弃她
You know, I would give her up for you.
不行  我不可以让你这样做的
No, I couldn't let you do that.
-但我想这样做  -但我不想你这样做
- No, but I want to. - But I don't want you to.
-但我坚持  -但我更坚持
- But I insist. - But I insist harder.
女生们  停一停好吗  我们投硬币决定吧
Girls. Girls. Stop. Okay, we'll flip a coin.
正面  她是瑞秋的
Heads, she's Rachel's.
反面  她就是莫尼卡的
Tails, she's Monica's.
反面  莫尼卡  她是你的了
Tails. Monica, she's yours.
不行  它掉到你的食物里了
No, that landed in your food.
不  没关系
No, no, that's okay.
你赢得光明正大  我太难过了
You won fair and square. I'm so sad.
嘿  乔伊
Hey, Joe?
-什么事  -坏消息
- What's up? - Bad news.
我看过了带子
I watched the tape
并把它交给我的老板们
and passed it along to my bosses
但他们不感兴趣
and they weren't interested.
对不起  老兄
I'm sorry, man.
但...你看过这带子吗
But you watched the tape?
是啊  我...我很喜欢啊
Yeah, I liked it.
但...我的老板不喜欢
But my bosses didn't go for it.
这些愚蠢的狗杂种
Stupid sons of bitches.
你没有看过这带子
You didn't watch the tape.
什么  我当然看啦
What? Of course I did.
你不推荐我是一回事
Look, it's one thing not to cast me,
但你对我说谎
but to lie to me?
我没有说谎啊  我看了啦
I'm not lying to you. I watched it.
你看  又说谎
You lied again.
-我看了  -继续说谎吧  匹诺曹
- I watched it. - Keep going, Pinocchio.
-我看了  -没有  你没看
- I did. - No, you didn't.
我告诉你  我看了这带子
I'm telling you, I watched the tape.
-你看过这带子吗  -没有
- Did you watch the tape? - No.
评选委员会选出
All right. The selection committee has chosen
你们三人于今天作最后评核
the three of you as our finalists.
最终决定会基于
The ultimate decision will be based on the answers
你们如何回答我的问题
you give to the questions I ask.
先从李博士开始吧
We're gonna go ahead and start with Dr. Li.
李博士  你提出学界
Dr. Li, you claim the field is too reliant
太依赖林奈分类系统
on the Linnaean taxonomic system.
那你打算怎么解决这个问题
How do you propose to correct this problem?
我相信解决办法
Well, I believe that the answers
在骨骼证据上
lie in the osteological evidence.
-我打算从那里入手  -很有趣
- I plan to begin there. - Interesting.
是吧
I guess.
白莉博士  你的方案有一些挖掘工作
Dr. Biely, your proposal includes some fieldwork.
你会选择哪里
Where might that take place?
首先是南达科他州的皮尔页岩地区
Primarily in the Pierre Shale region of South Dakota.
当然  很好
Certainly. Very well.
那盖勒博士  我生日是什么时候
And Dr.Geller, when is my birthday?
什么  我...
What? I--
不能猜一下吗
Care to venture a guess?
-5月12号  -还差很远呢
- May 12? - That's not even kind of close.
李博士  你需要多少个研究生呢
Dr. Li, how many graduate students you'd be needing?
六个
Half a dozen.
明白了  那白莉博士呢
I see. And Dr. Biely?
三个负责挖掘  两个负责分析
Three for excavation, and two for analysis.
当然  盖勒博士  1965年沙伦斯乐队
Certainly. Dr. Geller, which 1965 Shirelles hit...
被哪支英国乐队盖过风头
...was later covered by a popular British Invasion band?
什么...  我需要六个研究生
What? I need six graduate students.
不是  对不起
No, I'm sorry.
答案是  "宝贝  就是你"
We were looking for "Baby It's You."
"宝贝  就是你"
"Baby It's You."
什么...  等等  等一下
What? Wait just a minute.
我的问题没有一条是关于古生物学的
None of my questions have anything to do with paleontology.
没错  我该道歉
You're right, I apologize.
那最后一条问题
Scratch the last question.
拼写单词"Boscodictiasaur"
Spell "Boscodictiasaur."
我没有听过这个单词啊
I've never heard of a "Boscodictiasaur."
是  我乱编的单词  快拼
Yeah, I just made it up. Spell it.
好的  B...O...S...
Okay. B-O-S-
不  开头有个不发音的"M"
No, it starts with a silent M.
拜托
Oh, come on!
我不敢相信乔伊这么说我
I can't believe Joey.
我讨厌被人称为骗子
I hate being called a liar.
但你就是个骗子
But you are a liar.
我刚刚怎么说的
What did I just say?
你还在啊
Are you still here?
是的  而且我不得不说
Yes. And I have to say.
我不仅仅是受伤害  我感觉被侮辱了一样
And I'm not just hurt, I'm insulted.
当我说我已经做了某事...
When I tell somebody I did something--
好了好了...  我打断你一下好吗
Okay, hold on, let me just stop you right there, okay?
首先  你说谎  对吗
First, you lied. Right?
然后  你又说谎去圆谎  好吗
Then you lied about lying, okay?
然后  你又再说谎
Then you lied about
去圆你刚才圆的谎
lying about lying, okay?
所以在你说谎去圆你刚才
So before you lie about
为圆谎...而说的谎...的那个谎言...
lying about lying about lying about lying....
不要说谎啦
Stop lying.
为什么你这么肯定
Why are you so sure
我没有看过那带子
I didn't watch this tape?
你想知道...
You wanna know why?
你想知道为什么
事情发展得不错呢
Well, this is going well.
这就是我知道你没看的原因了
Here's how I know you didn't watch.
如果你看了这带子
If you had seen what was on this tape,
你绝对不会没有话说的
believe me, you'd have some comments.
听好  我收了很多钱才去拍这个广告
All right, remember, I got paid a lot of money for this...
而且只在日本地区放映
...and it only aired in Japan.
一级棒
Ichiban.
一级棒  男用唇膏
Ichiban, lipstick for men.
这就是我知道你没看的原因
And that's how I know you didn't watch the tape.
他真的是一条变色龙呢
He really is a chameleon.
格拉达斯  跟你的新家打个招呼吧
Well, Gladys, say hello to your new home.
-我的... -哇
- Oh, my. - Wow.
她真漂亮  又显眼
Oh, she is so nice and big.
莫尼卡  你会把她放到什么地方
Oh, Monica, where are you going to display Gladys,
你得多骄傲啊
oh, so proudly?
我还没决定放在哪里
I haven't really settled on a spot yet.
那不如放在电视机上面吧
How about right above the TV?
这样的话  人们一进门
That way, it will be the first thing that you see
就马上看得到了
when you walk in the door.
好啊  好啊
Yeah, yeah,
那你就可以丢掉那法国的海报了
and you can get rid of that French poster.
-我喜欢那海报啊  -是吗
- I like that poster. - Really?
它没有东西可以"冒"出来啊
It doesn't have anything coming out of it.
又或者你的卧室里有空位吗
Or maybe there's someplace for her in your bedroom?
噢  你床头还空着呢
There's nothing above your bed.
你怎么还在这
Are you still here?
噢  嗨  你好
Oh, hi. Hello.
你是来问我古生物学的问题的吗
Have you come to ask me some more paleontology-related questions?
可能你要问我你祖母的昵称吧
Your grandmother's nickname, perhaps?
还是你马格莉特阿姨内裤的尺寸
Aunt Margaret's pants size?
我是来道歉的
I've come here to apologize.
我想我对查莉的感情…
I think I may have let my feelings...
影响到面试的程序了
...for Charlie interfere with the interview process.
没有  哪里有
No. Stop.
不管怎么说  我决定把资金批给你
Anyway, I decided to offer you the grant.
真的吗
Really?
只是还有一个条件
There is just one small stipulation.
我要和查莉分手
I have to break up with Charlie?
嘿  你终于答对一次了
Hey, you got one right.
你发神经
You're crazy.
神经  还是...浪漫
Crazy or romantic?
神经
Crazy.
-还是...  -出去
- Or? - Get out!
噢  天啊
Oh, my God.
什么
What?
乔伊  这东西在这里干嘛
Joey, what is this thing doing here?
我在莫尼卡那里拿过来的
I got her from Monica.
她出了个很合理的价格
She sold it to me for a very reasonable price.
乔伊  我们不能留着这个
Joey, we're not keeping this.
但它是原版的布菲作品啊...
But it's an original Buffay.
好的  没关系  你就留着吧
All right, fine. You can keep it.
只要你不介意她有灵魂附体
As long as you don't mind that she's haunted.
嘿  什么...
Hey, what? What?
有这样一个传说  乔伊
Well, legend has it, Joey,
她在你半夜睡觉的时候会活过来
that she comes alive when you're asleep.
她爬出这画框
She climbs out of the frame...
然后她拖着她这半个身体
...and then drags her half-a-body
爬在地板上
across the floor...
想办法去偷一双腿
...just looking for legs to steal.
然后她用她唯一的一只手
And then with her one good hand...
慢慢地...
...she slowly reaches up...
扭开门把手
...and turns your doorknob.
拿走这没脚的妖怪
Get that legless witch out of here!
嘿  我把它卖给乔伊了
Hey, I sold that to Joey.
所以我骗他这是鬼怪了
Yeah, well, I told him it's haunted.
我们都会玩这种把戏
Two can play at this game.
不行  太迟了  你不能退货
Too late. You can't give it back.
我当然可以
Oh, yes, I can.
不  你不可以  她是你的
No, you can't, she's yours.
-她是你的  -是你的
- She's yours. - She's yours.
她是你的
She's yours.
嘿
Hey.
-她是我的  -是我的
- She's mine. - She's mine.
-她是我的  -她是我的
你们啊  不用为她争吵了
You guys, you don't have to fight over her anymore.
谁得不到格拉达斯
Whoever doesn't get Gladys,
就把格林妮斯拿回去吧
gets Glynnis.
-我要格拉达斯  -她是我的
- I want Gladys. - She's mine.
-她是我的  -她是我的
- She's mine. - She's mine.
很抱歉我没有把你的带子给他们
I know. Look, I'm sorry I didn't give them your tape.
我保证  下次无论合不合适
And I promise next time to submit you,
我都会把你推荐上去的
whether I think you're right or not.
重点不是这个啊  钱德勒
That's not the point, Chandler.
重点是  你说了谎
The point is that you lied.
我知道  你说的对
I know. You're right.
我要做什么你才能原谅我
What's it gonna take for you to forgive me?
噢  天啊
Oh, my God.
绝了
Excellent.
现在你该说什么
Now what do you say?
说谎是不对的
Lying is wrong.
还有呢...  还有呢...
And? And?
我是个漂亮美眉
I'm a pretty little girl.
我早就知道啦
I knew it.
你的前男友是个疯子
Your ex-boyfriend is insane.
随便啦  你得到那笔资金了吗
Did you get the grant?
没有  你想知道为什么吗
No. And you wanna know why?
因为你的前男友还是爱着你
Because your ex-boyfriend is still in love with you.
-什么  -没错
- What? - Yeah.
他没有给我那笔补助
He wouldn't give me the grant,
就因为我没有放弃你
because I wouldn't give you up.
本杰不会还爱着我的
Benji isn't in love with me.
因为当时是他抛弃我
I mean, he broke up with me.
而且  他是个很有道德的人
And besides, he's a very ethical man.
是吗
Really?
在面谈中问这种问题
Is it ethical to ask someone in a grant review:
《超狗任务》中谁给狗配音
"Who was the voice of Underdog?"
我肯定他是在开玩笑  罗斯
I'm sure he was just joking, Ross.
如果你不相信我  我们去找他对质吧
If you don't believe me, let's go talk to him.
可以告诉你
I'm telling you,
他没有问过我一个关于考古学的问题
he didn't ask me one paleontological question.
真的吗
Seriously?
哦  不是  他问了我一个
Oh, I'm sorry. No, he did ask me one:
怎么拼"boscodictiosaur"
"How do you spell Boscodictiasaur?"
和刚果的巴斯克湖拼法一样
Well, if it's like the Lake Mbosco in Congo,
那是M...B...O...
then M-B-O--
可恶
Damn it.
盖勒博士...  查莉  你们到这来干什么
Dr. Geller. Charlie, what are you doing here?
我要你告诉他一切
I want you to tell her everything.
告诉他你想和我做的交易
About the deal you tried to make with me,
那些神经病的问题
about the crazy questions you--
沃利·考克斯  他就是《超狗任务》的配音
Wally Cox. That's the voice of Underdog.
就如之前的调查我告诉你一样
Like I tried to tell you in the interview...
这笔资金不是为了
...this grant is not based on
这些无聊的知识而设的
your knowledge of pretty useless trivia.
不  不  不  别这样
No, don't do that.
我要你看着她的眼睛
I want you to look her in the eyes
告诉她真相
and tell her the truth.
本杰
Benji?
是的  的确是这样
All right. It's true.
我之前简直是乱来
I behaved horribly,
但这都是因为我还爱着你
but it's only because I still love you.
只要你回到我身边
And I would do anything
我可以做任何事
to have you back in my life.
早干嘛去了  本杰
Too little, too late, Benji.
我不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我真不应该离开你
I never should've broken up with you.
我无时无刻不在想你
I think about you all the time.
难道你就从来没想过我吗
Do you ever still think about me?
没有
No.
-有  -什么
- Yes. - What?
我不知道该说什么好了  本杰
I don't know what to say, Benji.
这一切实在太...
This is all so...
浪漫了
...romantic.
或者...
Or?
我知道  或者我做得太过火了
I know I may be way out of bounds here...
但我们还有机会在一起吗
...but is there any chance you would take me back?
或者可以...
Maybe.
甜心  你们的对话
Sweetie, this conversation is starting to
让我觉得有点不舒服了
make me a little uncomfortable.
天啊  我很抱歉  但...
Oh, God. I am so sorry, but--
我是说...我们之前有太多的过去了...
I mean, there's so much history between us, you know?
我也觉得抱歉...
I'm sorry too.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
好吧就这样  我们都可以找下家了
Okay, that's it, we are seeing other people.
格拉达斯
Gladys?
这个星期的第三次了
For the third time this week.
天啊  真是常玩常新啊
Man, this does not get old.
你真可恶
You're mean!
不要这么孩子气啦
Oh, don't be such a baby. Please.